Worked on the series:
Lily, Tiramisu, Zinger, Pineapple, Host, Biryulka
How did I become
queen
FANSUB GROUP AZALIA PRESENTS
All characters are fictitious
and the events shown are fiction.
Episode 5
Every person has their own weakness.
Even Superman when encountering kryptonite
becomes just a weirdo
who wears underpants over his pants.
If Superman is so weak,
imagine what happens to ordinary people.
I will reveal the truth!
I will accept your will, Your Majesty!
It's not her who needs to be executed!
Your Majesty!
I beg you.
Will you go against the will of the king?
For the average person, this world is a minefield of weaknesses.
We become each other's weakness
and drag everyone into the underworld.
Even I, the perfect Jang Bong Hwan, have weaknesses.
And this is nothing more than...
I can't stand it when another guy looks cooler than me.
Harm the queen...
Stop!
Especially in the presence of the one I like.
I must be the coolest in her eyes.
You could say this is the Achilles heel of
who is perfection itself.
Let me, as a victim of this incident,
shed light on events.
I
tried to commit suicide.
Do you think there's only one cool guy here?
Don't worry, Cheoljong.
I'm the hero here.
I ask you, do not touch those who are innocent of anything.
Great.
What a ridiculous statement?
The Dowager Queen.
I'm sorry, but I tried to kill myself.
Leave your false self
I carried this suicide note with me.
I'll still be back today.
I don't care if chaos reigns here.
Why are you doing this?
And why would you kill yourself?
the night before you become queen?
The thing is...
What was your reason?
Well I was depressed
and I wanted to die because...
I'm sure there was a reason.
Your Highness!
Crap!
Your Majesty!
Soyeon.
Will he take me away now?
Don't you dare.
Don't come near. Away!
The Dowager Queen.
The Queen is telling lies
to save a life
to a less important person than her.
Trust your virtuous heart
forgiving the one
who committed a sin against her,
and show mercy.
So this is how he took it all?
What's so interesting about this?
So many people gathered.
Yours...
Your Majesty.
What happened here?
Fine.
The queen put in so much effort
so be it, I will show mercy.
Episode 5: Achilles' Heel
I haven't seen such a sight for a long time.
I wonder what the queen was thinking when she did that.
Such is the heart of a woman.
But I'm sure the Kims have nothing to do with it.
Yes.
Heading to Sonongjeong Hall?
Today I need something more than prayer.
She's just a weak royal consort
but she is our only arrow.
You need to apply poison to its tip.
Gods.
Did she try to commit suicide?
What does it mean?
I'll bide my time and wake up at the right moment.
What kind of father am I that I didn’t guess?
I have committed a great sin.
I have sinned.
It's all my fault.
He should have taken better care of her.
I missed it.
Why did she do this?
You should know, you are with her all the time.
She tried to jump into the water several times,
I thought it was because of the shock during the fall.
Several times?
How did she suffer?
Your Majesty.
Well damn, that's enough already.
If you cry, I won’t wake up.
Now is not the time to cry.
He will see us in tears,
will be very upset.
Certainly.
You're right.
At such moments you need to be brave and be close to her.
Should I wake up now?
-Soyeon.
- Damn it.
When your mother gave you life
she lost hers.
Has he started again?
Your Majesty.
Her Majesty has grown
not having a chance to see my mother's face.
I feel so sorry for her.
I don't know why she suffered so much
and I only forbade her this and that.
I chased her
and grumbled all the time.
It was because of me that she could
jump into the lake.
How so, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty!
I give up.
I can't handle this situation.
Gwanghwamun
My queen.
Please
take care of yourself.
Your pathetic father
asks for forgiveness.
Benin.
Today I will enter the palace.
I will meet the king for the first time.
So happy?
I'm just curious.
Sometimes he looks like an ugly idiot
and sometimes as if made of jade.
In my dreams.
Last night he looked exactly like you.
I believed that I should give up on you
to make you happy.
Before visiting the palace, you were so happy.
However, after visiting the palace she tried to commit suicide.
Is it really because of this?
She's gone crazy! I've lost the rest of my mind!
Leave your false self
She spent several nights with the king.
Are you sure
that he didn't cloud her brain?
Calm down, Your Majesty.
Your anger is of little use.
How can I not be angry?
We missed a great opportunity.
They shot themselves in the foot!
Did you see how the king behaved?
That arrogant look.
I saved him from the life of a simple peasant and made him a king,
and he dares to look like that?
We need to pacify him, since he is rebelling.
I will tighten the rules so that I know my place.
Why waste time taking care of yourself?
There is no trace of effort, it’s worth worrying.
Invite doctor Pak.
Yes.
To be honest, the queen came to see me.
That night when I threw myself into the lake.
Dowager Queen, I
I'll leave the palace.
What are you talking about?
I can't become queen.
I don’t want such a bitter fate for myself.
I've heard rumors
that you're behaving terribly
but it was all on purpose,
so as not to become a queen.
How nice.
You thought you could achieve something with this.
You took classes to become a queen.
I don't know why I suddenly changed my mind
and I don’t want to know.
Your destiny was predetermined from birth.
You must become a queen and serve your family.
This is your destiny, this is what you were born for.
Have you taken this position yourself?
No, not myself.
So you can't back down
even if you want to.
If you want to die, die in the palace.
I thought she said that because
that young people are now inclined to make mountains out of molehills.
Therefore, I didn’t attach much importance to it.
I couldn't even think that she jumped into the lake,
to commit suicide.
If she was ready to die
just not to become a queen,
That means her crazy behavior today too...
A way to step down as queen.
If this is the case,
the queen will not escape unpunished.
Wait for me! What if you fall?
I told you, don't rush.
Who dares to block my path?
The Dowager Queen.
You won't be able to return home.
-What?
-To the Queen, Jang Bong Hwan,
ordered to stay here forever until the end of his days
and live in agony, remaining impotent.
No.
I don't want.
I don't want to be impotent!
Your Majesty!
What a terrible nightmare.
You tried to drown yourself in the lake,
and today they fainted, I was so scared...
Calm down. I understand how you feel.
I will die with you!
Enough already.
I've had enough tears for today, I can't stand it anymore.
It’s not contagious, so why did you cry three times?
I fell asleep while I was waiting for you to stop.
Of course you don't want to see my tears.
You're cute when you smile.
Where is Court Lady Choi?
She insisted that she would bring you the medicine herself.
Your father stayed with you
and went home only after sunset.
If only we had woken up a little earlier, we would have seen it.
Thank heavens I didn't see him.
What?
If he knew what a beautiful body
his priceless daughter was captured by the man's soul,
I would be upset.
We must hurry before Lady Choi returns.
The lake has already been filled, hasn't it?
Do you want to go to the lake at this time?
Today is the last day.
-Are you in a good mood?
- Of course.
All that's left is to return home,
remaining the coolest guy here.
Oh, exactly.
-Honyoung.
-Yes, queen.
I was able to endure all this thanks to you.
I don't know about the others, but I'll miss you.
Yes, and I will also miss Court Lady Choi.
Hongyong, leave this will to your descendants.
Will?
Buy land in Gangnam.
You have to tell them this.
Then after 200 years
your heirs will live like rich people.
That's all I can give you.
Okay, go ahead.
Your Majesty, be careful.
More energetic.
Hurry up, need to hurry up.
What is this?
Why did we go back to the old way?
when did I come up with a new system?
The thing is...
The well is empty.
Because we take water from another
and bring it here, but...
Will you repeat it again? I heard something wrong.
It sounded like you weren't going to finish today.
Forgive us, queen.
-Forgive us, queen.
A high-ranking official must keep his word.
You promised to fill the lake today.
Nearest well
It's very, very far from here.
It will take at least 15 days...
Please execute me!
-Please, execute me!
-Please, execute me.
Why do you keep asking for execution?
Don’t you believe that I will actually execute you?
Should I demonstrate it to you?
Do you want to experience for yourself what kind of scam happens?
Let's go. I'm sure even an incomplete lake will work.
No, Your Majesty.
Why are you doing this?
I won't let you take your life again.
It's not like that at all.
I'm not trying to die.
What are you trying to do then?
In short...
I'm trying to survive. That's the only way I can do it!
You will only pass over my corpse!
Damn, where do you have so much strength?
Get off me.
If this granny changes her mind
and get rid of the water in the lake again, I’m screwed!
Help stop the queen!
How dare you touch her?
Your Majesty!
I beg you, no!
From now on, no quibbles!
I will never tell you “no”!
You can't do that!
She said you wouldn't.
That you can never say “no”!
Damn it.
It won't work.
Yes, at least tickle it.
I forgot how to laugh a long time ago.
Crap.
I won't. Let's go.
That's it.
Damn, I'm stuck.
So you don't want me to go there?
Great.
Raise your head.
Straighten your back.
Can you swim?
Is that all?
I'll go further, it will be deeper there.
Okay, move it.
-Fathers.
-Yes, here it is!
I tripped!
- Bummer.
-Your Majesty.
The Queen Dowager calls for your presence at once.
Damn you!
Lee Senman. This name backfired on me.
Crap.
-Miracle.
-What bliss.
Like this.
What's happened?
Do you sometimes have this feeling too?
When everyone is fussing around, but no one cares about you.
Sir, you are the center of the universe for me.
Well, sensitive people like me
sometimes they make mistakes in their premonitions, like today.
I didn't order naengmyeon.
You make me happy every night by allowing me to serve you.
This is from the bottom of my heart.
Let me say something.
It may seem like I'm hanging around here for fun, but that's not the case.
I'm just here to find out something
about Lee Senman, who suddenly disappeared.
But why are you looking for him so desperately?
It feels like behind his disappearance
there is an important secret hidden.
My sixth sense tells me
what is this Lee Sanman
at the very center of the problem.
-What problem?
-I have no idea.
What?
They're checking me now.
-About today...
-It's my fault.
I forced you to marry him against your will.
Don't you really want to be queen?
So much so that you are ready to say goodbye to life?
And be deposed as queen?
Did she try to commit suicide so she wouldn't be queen?
Great.
If you want it so desperately
I will let you leave the palace.
I will bring you down.
You will be confined in your home
and you won’t step outside the threshold for the rest of your life.
No.
I can only get back through the lake here.
I don't remember this.
After falling into the lake, I forgot about everything.
Memories didn't come back
but did you remember that you wanted to commit suicide?
I still have a feeling of pain.
And I'm sure I embroidered this note.
But I don’t know why I wanted to commit suicide.
If you don't remember anything,
why did you interfere?
If you don't give a reason,
I will consider that you opposed me.
No.
And I had no intention of resisting you.
Today you undermined my authority.
I need to fix this.
But I don't have a solution. Damn, nothing comes to mind.
And I can't forgive you for that.
I deserve to die, Your Majesty.
Take my life.
I'm confused because of the lack of memories
but I can't turn away from my kind
and from my husband.
Please punish me
give poison to get rid of this pain.
They certainly don't want to overthrow the queen.
Is it that easy for you to give up your life?
She threw herself into the lake.
Now do you want to drink poison?
Why are you so weak?
They want to make sure
that they have power over the queen.
My stupid decision to say goodbye to life
gave rise to all this misunderstanding.
My action is worthy of death.
I beg you to execute me, Your Majesty.
Your death won't fix anything.
Because of this trick
the Queen Mother will gain an advantage.
But this will not only affect you.
This will affect the entire Kim family.
-I'll try...
-Calm down, please.
I'll ask you for the last time.
Do you really want to leave the palace?
I want
live in a palace.
What do you think, Your Majesty?
Since I have no memories left, I will become a new person.
I will become the perfect queen.
I don't believe in empty promises.
I'll prove it in practice.
Please give her a chance, Your Majesty.
Fine.
Thank you for your kindness.
I won't bother you anymore.
There's nothing to worry about.
"Leave Your False Self"
Because we no longer have weaknesses.
We will eliminate
any problem.
He will do it.
This is a warning.
Everything is so unclear.
Shall we light more lanterns, Your Majesty?
No. This is me talking about my future.
Prince Yeonpyeong and his men searched the palace.
His people?
Were these the royal guards?
They are well trained.
How many?
A little.
-Seven.
-For all this time
they secretly trained only seven?
You're out of medicine.
If it weren't for the disease, you would have become an excellent warrior.
I'm still alive
only thanks to your help.
Thank you.
If you make a mistake again,
You won't get any more medicine.
I'll remember.
Until now
we thought that the queen fell into the lake to frame Concubine Cho.
We thought she was deliberately lying about losing her memories.
I can't believe she tried to commit suicide.
Perhaps this is how she wanted to gain your trust.
Do you think she knew that I would protect Concubine Cho?
Don't stand up for her
the queen would have blamed her.
She realized
that can influence you in this way.
Prince Yeonpyeong, you see
There is evil intent in every action of the queen.
Queen -
support of the Kim family.
What kind of people are they?
They are the ones who massacred our entire family.
I never
I won't be able to forget this.
I won't forget this either.
But look what the queen did.
Despite my attempt to kill her and my enmity with Concubine Cho,
she revealed the truth for our sake.
Still think your hostility towards her
deserved?
-Your Majesty.
-If it was a suicide attempt,
then I killed the queen twice.
Why are you here?
I need to talk to you.
You're only making things more complicated.
My fate is already in the hands of your family.
Next time I'll just pass on the letter.
You don't like me
because I am from the Andong family of Kim?
I didn't say I didn't like you.
Then do you like me?
If I were not from the Andong family of Kim,
Would you like me?
No, I don't think so.
You became queen thanks to your family.
I put in a lot of effort.
I didn't want to become queen because of my family.
I dedicated my whole life to this, no matter what they say.
Tomorrow you will get what you so desperately wanted.
It's late, and tomorrow will be a difficult day.
Return to your quarters.
You must love me.
Is this an order?
My indifference made her jump into the lake.
If she tried to commit suicide because of your indifference,
she would just jump into the lake.
But she forged the letter and fell in front of Concubine Cho.
I see an ulterior motive here.
Motive, you say.
I need to see the queen.
The attackers don't hide their smile.
If there was an ulterior motive behind her actions,
I can tell by her behavior.
Take care of Concubine Cho for now.
Pretend to be the perfect queen for 15 days.
Can I handle it?
If I can’t, then I’ll remain in this suffocating body,
Moreover, behind bars as a deposed queen in the Joseon era.
He dug his own grave. Who else is to blame?
Your Majesty, the king has arrived.
Of course Cheoljong.
It's all his fault.
I wouldn't stand up for her
if only he weren't so cool.
Open it up.
And even before that, he completely blundered.
This woman wouldn't try
drown himself, if he were nicer to her.
-No, if he had before...
-My queen.
How do you feel?
You put a sword to my neck,
where does this concern come from?
I haven't had a single quiet day here.
I just opened my eyes, and tomorrow is the wedding.
The husband with whom I share the same blanket is trying to kill me.
And even your own family
threatens to overthrow me.
Overthrow?
What? Tempting?
What a good opportunity to replace me with Cho Hwajin, right?
Why are you so excited?
I didn't come to fight with you.
Just looking at you makes me angry.
Have you thought about it?
You who tried to kill me
and the one for whom you are ready to die.
I'm about to die trying to save you two.
Yes, they will kill me before I commit suicide.
Anyone in my place would be angry right now if he weren't Buddha.
I understand that you are very angry with me.
Stop.
No need.
Don't you dare say
that you understand me.
You should have understood me
before putting the sword to my neck.
No. You should have understood this woman before
how she tried to commit suicide.
The moment has passed. There's no point in saying anything.
Leave already. I was tired while I was angry.
I'll come back when you feel better.
Don't come unless you're ready to beg on your knees.
I'll come back.
She told me not to come!
Are they refilling the lake?
Her Majesty asked the Queen Dowager about this.
For what?
I don't know exactly
but I heard Her Majesty went to the lake
and personally monitored everything.
Your Majesty.
Sorry to bother you.
I was afraid that I might lose you.
Are you injured?
Your wound hurts more,
than mine.
Today
it was very hard for you.
I'm sorry I got you into this.
It must have been so hard for you
because of all these problems in the palace.
I don't want you to suffer.
So don't do it again.
If you sacrifice yourself for me,
How will I deal with this?
I won't do what you're afraid of.
Until everything settles down,
Prince Yeonpyeong will personally guard you.
What about Ovol?
-Well...
- Mister Hong has arrived.
Come in.
As Concubine Cho's maid?
She's in the infirmary now.
My brother will take care of everything.
Thank you.
Have you met the queen?
Yes.
-How is she?
-She was angry.
-What?
-Blamed me
that he drove her to suicide.
Hates me for trying to kill her.
Emotions overwhelm her.
If she wanted to win me over,
I wouldn't behave like that.
And one more thing
The Kims are threatening to overthrow her.
Kim Byungin doesn't know yet
that that scrap is from your clothes.
Fine.
The Queen said nothing.
I don't know her intentions
but it seems to work on its own.
I thought I'd understand
what kind of person she is, based on her actions.
But she only puzzled me more.
Father, this is Benin.
Yes. Come in.
I thought you quit smoking.
Quit.
I'm sorry about today.
Why are you apologizing?
What will you do next?
I'll try to reason with her.
And if she doesn't understand, she won't exist.
Who are you talking about?
About anyone.
There is no such thing as an ally for centuries.
I'm afraid now is not the time for this,
but I have to tell.
Fine. What's there?
I decided how far I would go with my dream.
I'm very glad to hear this.
What kind of position?
I will be the head of the Detective Department.
Detective department?
Is being a warrior everything you dreamed of?
I'll start with a position I can handle
and choose my path.
How's that?
You say you want to choose your own path?
The royal concubine has arrived.
Do not move.
Your Highness.
Sorry.
I had to stand until the last.
Your broken knees are proof.
I know.
It's nothing.
A couple of days with medicinal herbs,
and I'll be up in no time.
Yes. I have no doubt you will get better.
Who could treat you so cruelly?
I didn’t see his face, he was wearing a mask.
But I remember the voice.
Your Highness.
I'm sorry for saying this.
If someone not from the royal family gets hurt,
he cannot stay in the palace.
But how can she leave in such a state?
This is a palace custom.
You can't expect compassion in this place.
If anyone is on the way
tries to harm you, use it as a bribe.
You will successfully leave the palace,
take advantage of this to live in comfort.
No, too much.
I will send a letter to my family.
Don't worry.
Thank you for your service.
I'm too ashamed to look at Mr. Cho's face.
I can't go.
Ovol, you and I grew up together.
You are my family.
You have to hang in there
so that I can too.
Be brave for me.
You must live.
Do it for me.
-What happened?
-Yesterday I was a madhouse.
Queen...
My lord.
Have you heard?
His Majesty through the eyes of thunder and lightning
threw at the dowager queen.
The eyes were like apples.
Hey you.
His Majesty picked it up right in front of the Queen and...
Royal chef, have you heard?
His Majesty grabbed the sword,
and the Queen Dowager...
Did you hear what happened in the Tonggunjong Hall?
I heard they do this all the time.
Will be appointed today
head of the Detective Department.
Will?
We have a request for an appointment.
And who was recommended?
for the post of head of the Detective Department?
Byonin from the Andong Kim clan.
Quite unexpected.
I'm sure there are many candidates for this position.
If I appoint as head the one
who passed the civil servant exam,
there will be complaints, don’t you think?
We unanimously agreed
with this recommendation.
Unanimously?
I didn't expect such a harmonious relationship
among my subjects.
I heard he is a wonderful person.
Is the royal notice of appointment already prepared?
To keep up with your fast-paced decisions,
maybe I should cut down on my sleep time.
Don't say that.
You need to take care of your health
and produce an heir.
Not a king, but a breeding horse.
You have always been humble.
Don't lose it - humility.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Pungyang Cho clan
brought trouble upon himself.
Because of the concubine's false confession
we have suffered such humiliation.
Failure is a cause, not a result.
What?
That's what the Queen Mother said.
We agreed with the appointment of Kim Byungin
and helped them strengthen their positions,
because they lost.
The more defeats, the less
our chances of winning.
She said,
we must take the first step.
Do you think Ovol will be able to recover?
I'll check how she's feeling.
She is active, so she constantly runs around.
Now he can’t do that anymore.
If she had not come to the palace with me...
Don't think about it too often.
Sometimes thoughts can drive you into a swamp.
And the harder you fight, the deeper it goes.
It will hurt even more.
What are you doing
to clear your head from the abundance of thoughts?
I
I'm going to Mr. Hong.
He can comfort you.
He's such a fool.
It drives me crazy.
And when I take it out on him,
then I get out of the swamp without even noticing it.
Then can you make me angry?
-This...
-Or...
Don't move.
I'm done.
What's happened?
It's okay.
Does something hurt?
You can't touch me.
I got a cramp.
It was a long time, right?
Thank heavens.
You were so focused that you forgot about time.
If you want to embroider,
then I had to go to the Daejojeon Hall.
What did you forget in the kitchen?
Do you really embroider anything?
I promised to transform myself into a model queen.
Exemplary, right?
Is there nothing to do? Give me some work?
My back.
And when will I figure all this out?
What's happened?
-Bring it in.
-Wait.
Is this from Dongmyeongjeong Hall?
-Yes, Your Majesty.
-Come on.
She tasted my dishes
the old ones now seem boring to her.
Okay. Take this to the stables.
If they are a palanquin for food
cover with a blanket of this size,
the food will not cool down.
Tell them to try.
Fine.
Will you rush to the lake as soon as you get rid of me?
Have you ever seen anyone work so hard and plan to die?
And you seem to have forgotten
this has become the norm,
but I’m somehow under CCTV cameras.
What are you even worried about?
Well, let's go create miracles?
Your Majesty!
Yes!
Hey there. Did you chop the meat?
Yes.
Get here quickly.
Bring me some salt.
The Queen wants me to serve it to her first.
That's it.
Well, well, do what you want.
Let's see what happens.
Maybe ask the queen to cook?
Your Majesty, this is the Chief Inspector.
The Queen has prepared lunch for you.
Should I tell him to take it away?
Mommies.
What's happened?
Well, there is no delicacy at all.
Your Majesty.
Your lunch arrived, but...
Be careful.
And this...
The queen said that
The theme of today's lunch is HSNV.
HSNV?
I've never heard of this before.
Is this Mencius?
No, it's not.
Maybe from the Analects of Confucius?
This means that
food is crispy on the outside
and tender inside.
Is it true?
The food palanquin has arrived!
Here. Take the plates.
Carefully.
Your Majesty.
She was very pleased and praised you.
I saw a palanquin for food
and asked how you feel about it
such a wonderful idea came.
The stump was clear, the result was obvious.
This thing was popular
in competitive Korea.
Joseon delivery man.
Oh, how proud I am of myself.
Generally speaking, women from the royal family
should always be modest.
you on me
Are you grumbling now, or what?
Should we be modest?
That was the question.
Nope. Life is hard, even if
you live off your pride.
I have no idea what he's talking about
but it still infuriates.
We should be glad that Ovol was able to survive.
This is a ray of hope in the darkness of failure.
I'm sure after what happened
you understand better now
What kind of people are the Kim clan?
I didn't think they were ready to go this far.
You must be scared.
However, this is just the beginning.
They will not forget this defeat.
There are rumors that the deceased king
did not die from illness.
It turns out...
He believed that the Kim clan was a plague on Joseon's body.
Do you know what you did wrong?
He deprived Kim Hong-geun of power
and sentenced him to exile.
King revises bribery law
so he
crossed the path of the Kim clan.
They are not the kind of people
who will sit idly by.
Fortunately,
luck was on the king's side,
and he found evidence against everyone who was behind these outrages.
After the death of the king
His food taster also disappeared.
I'm sure he was poisoned.
If only we were faster
the king would still be alive.
Listen to me
It's not over for you yet
but if you miss the moment, you won’t get anything back.
This time it was your maid Ovol who suffered,
but next time you will be in her place.
I'll file a petition
about depriving the queen of her title.
You don't even have to do anything
the king will come to meet us.
You will only have to approve this idea.
Queen Mother, please forgive me,
but I need your help.
All you have to do is take care of our king.
After this the king will change
his attitude towards the queen,
won't see why she's doing all this.
It's cloudy outside.
It looks like it's going to rain.
Court lady Han,
The room is dark, light the candles.
I obey.
If you wait for the king, he won't come.
How do you know that...
You'll just calm down
when will you take everything from me?
Have you changed the letter?
You changed something more serious.
Why can't I replace such a small thing?
I don't understand what you're talking about.
I know you lied.
If the king finds out the truth,
then you will understand my feelings.
The feeling you get
when you lose someone you care about.
How hard is it for you
will look into his eyes
for the rest of my life.
If you want to keep everything a secret, leave the palace.
You found my weak spot.
Okay, tell this to the king,
but then you will have to talk about something else.
Have you tried
kill the king.
So you know.
You have
nothing will come of it.
Someday you too will lose
person dear to you.
What's happened?
You already know.
His Majesty
weak when he feels guilty.
This is the price of survival.
Guilt.
Your Majesty, this is what you are willing to do,
to win the favor of the king?
Hurry up, clean it up before everything gets wet!
Hurry up!
It had been raining for several days now.
And finally he went.
In this life my position is higher than in the present one,
but why do I feel even worse?
Your Majesty,
Do you think I can have another life?
According to the theory of parallel worlds, everything is possible.
Look.
This is the life you are living now.
But this is your other life.
Understand?
Some kind of damn thing.
After I started talking
with the queen, spoke some gibberish.
Then could this puppy
to be human in a past life?
Anything is possible.
And the cook is a fool?
Otherwise... He was probably my subordinate.
What about me?
You will always be Choi's court lady.
And you, Hongyong...
Then my mom and dad
will they be happy in their next life?
What?
My mother only has four nails left.
She lost her nails
when I was sorting through stones in the cold winter.
In another life with my mother
will all the nails be in place?
Certainly.
And the priest will have two eyes!
What about your father?
-They gouged out his eye with a pitchfork.
-What?
Must have borrowed rice
and did not pay interest.
And the moneylenders then collect the debts.
In every yard there is someone
victimized by moneylenders.
Don't worry.
In your next life with your mother
there will be beautiful healthy nails,
You won't even need a manicure.
And father will have
His eyes are so sparkling, it’s like he’s wearing contacts.
I would like to see my mother with healthy nails.
Eh!
And I.
I really want to see my mother.
You didn't get to see your mother's face!
How so.
Well, why did you remember about her?
I'm not talking about this mom!
I'm talking about Ms. Li Sunxin, she is alive and well!
He even does Zumba!
Why do you make me feel like an orphan?
Gathered in the royal kitchen,
where the path is closed to women, and they whine.
I don't understand women.
Mommy?
Mommy!
It's raining, so everyone is sad.
Listen, bring me some pajeon and makgeolli.
Return to Daejojeon Hall.
The rain will continue to fall for a long time.
How do you know?
Have you become a meteorological computer?
I have no idea what you're talking about
but my wrist hurts a lot,
This means it will rain all night.
How strong?
I don't know
when it hurts so much, it means
All barrels will be filled in just a couple of hours.
Will it fill the barrels in a couple of hours?
Then will there be water in lakes and wells?
Chief Eunuch.
I'm listening, sir.
Book of Changes
So that our nights with the queen
were more productive
I'll go to bed after
I'll read a little more.
It's late, you can go.
I obey.
Notes on weapons and equipment
I'll come back when you feel better.
Don't come unless you're ready to beg on your knees.
She told me not to come!
Everyday I bend my knees
but not in front of whom
I should bow down.
Your Majesty!
You'll get sick!
I don’t care about illness!
Look, heaven is on my side!
My God, madam, stop it!
Please, calm down!
Your Majesty!
Your Majesty?
And one more time!
What are you talking about?
Like this! Hooray! Finally!
Your Majesty!
What's the matter with you?
What kind of woman is she?
You never know what's on her mind.
Like this! Wonderful!
What happened to you?
Why are you without a support group?
Also decided to take a walk in the rain?
I came to apologize.
Forget it, I don't care.
No,
I can't forget about it.
I’m telling you, I don’t care, why are you attached?
Got attached?
I'm a simple person.
I'm glad to see you - I'm swearing,
I'm grateful - I'm getting into a fight.
I can't stand sycophants
get out.
Leave?
I mustered up the courage to apologize
and this is what I get in response?
Listen, if the only person who needs an apology is
who apologizes, not the one who
who receives them, is this an apology?
The royal family has its own rules.
How long are you going to talk so strangely?
Only today. This is the last day.
And tomorrow everything will fall into place!
Like this! Oh yes!
Your Majesty!
-Like this!
-Queen!
Oh yes!
Your Majesty, come to your senses!
You offended me, so today we sleep separately.
Spend the night alone.
God bless! I'm so glad to hear this!
What a great guy I am.
Did you go outside without an umbrella?
Sometimes I like to take a walk without an umbrella.
I feel like the rain is washing away all my worries.
Don't be sad!
Your Majesty, go back inside!
What a nightmare! Empress!
Stop it!
What is this? Why would there be thunder?
Heaven is angry!
Get angry!
I move my pelvis if it means
that the rain will continue to pour for a long time!
Your Majesty! Stop it!
Oh yes!
Please!
Your Majesty!
The queen's illness is getting worse day by day,
she does not miss the chance to commit suicide.
The whole yard trembles from her antics.
Wouldn't it be better to file a petition?
about stripping her of her title?
-You're right.
-Right.
It's time for our clan
gather your strength.
When the enemy opens his defenseless neck,
you have to grab onto it right away.
The core of our country is in danger.
Stripping the queen of her title is the right decision.
Once upon a time there lived an immortal named Achilles.
And he had only one weak point.
Legends say
that he died from an arrow shot into his heel.
This is how the expression "Achilles' heel" came about.
But the real reason for his death is
that Achilles did not have what
who would make him armored shoes.
They say...
If people wanted to get rid
weak points, they would get rid of each other.
Avoid the threat...
We are each other's weak points
reasons why we suffer.
But we also protect and save each other.
Hongyong,
be sure to buy land in Gangnam.
Yes, Your Majesty.
Lady Choi,
You've been through a lot because of me.
Finally.
Lake Chhundaji
I shouldn't have gotten here
Jang Bong-hwan
We need to celebrate somehow.
Now everything will finally fall into place.
The Queen is the most unusual and strange person
of everyone I know.
It's like she's not from our world.
Whose soul do you want to evoke?
This woman has definitely gone crazy.
The internal crisis is much worse
external problem. Don't agree?
Do you want to say that in the country
Is there a problem that didn't exist before?
It turns out...
His Majesty's Interest in the Queen
will become our weakness.
Then today is our first day.
What?